今晚 这是一个你从未见过的单身总理
Tonight it's a bachelor premier like you've never seen before,
一切都从现在开始
and it all starts right now.
单身汉
Bachelor.
当然
Of course,
这意味着现在是一个全新赛季的时候了
that means it is time for a brand new season.
单身汉
The bachelor.
如果你不知道
If you couldn't tell,
我住在好莱坞的红地毯上
I am here live on the red carpet in Hollywood,
准备好了
getting ready,
今晚在全国范围内将会有数百万人在做这件事
put millions more are going to be doing all around the country tonight.
有现场观看派对
having live viewing parties.
你好
Hello,
每个人
everybody.
我是克里斯哈里森
I'm Chris Harrison.
这将是一个难以置信的夜晚 因为这个季节将会和我们以前所见过的任何东西都不一样
This promises to be an incredible night because this season will be unlike anything we have ever seen before.
今晚的节目是我们在节目中见过的最奇怪的玫瑰仪式
Tonight's episode features the strangest rose ceremony we have ever seen on the show,
这仅仅是个开始 因为这一季的人们已经有了
and that's just the beginning because this season folks it has at all.
我们有个处女在幻想的秋千上过夜
we've got a virgin who spends the night in the fantasy swing.
一个健康的年轻女孩 有一个X 超过了两个寡妇 希望有第二次机会去爱
A wholesome young girl with an X rated past two widows hoping for a second chance at love.
在美国 最受欢迎的脱口秀主持人之一 在为你的演讲做准备
and one of the most popular talk show host in America takes a shot at filling in for yours truly.
但在我们讨论所有这些以及红毯上的混乱之前
But before we get to all of that and all this chaos on the red carpet,
让我们去了解我们的新单身汉吧
let's get to know our new bachelor.
他们称之为 农业王子
the man they call Prince farming.
三十三岁来自阿林顿
Bristles thirty three years old from Arlington,
爱荷华州
Iowa.
高速公路
Highways,
上帝的国度
God's country.
城市中心和农民生活在一个小镇上
Urban centers and farmer living in a small town and on?
我觉得自己是最幸运的人
I feel like the luckiest man alive.
我真的不敢相信我是
I honestly can't believe I am.
下一个单身汉是不会发生的
The next bachelor doesn't happen.
像我这样的普通人
The normal guys like me.
是吗
The?
自从我第一次看我爸爸的时候
Since I was a kid watching my dad by his first time,
对她的农田的声音和热情
a voice and passion for her farmland,
我的祖父在40英亩的土地上开始耕作
my grandfather had started farming on forty acres.
现在我们有大约六千英亩的土地
and now we're up to approximately six thousand acres.
当你看到你的庄稼长势良好 长势良好时 你会有一种难以置信的自豪感和成就感
There's an incredible sense of pride and accomplishment when you can see your crops grow and flourish and do well.
也为能够养活世界而自豪 你将成为其中的一个重要部分
Also proud to be able to feed the world and you will be a big part of it.
有很多工作要做
It's a lot of work,
但是在你的土地上 有一些东西在外面或拖拉机上
but there's something about being outside or on a tractor on your land.
这就像其他的一样
That's like nothing else.
这是令人难以置信的回报
It's unbelievably rewarding.
但这也很有趣
But it's also just a lot of fun,
我喜欢做的事
something I love to do.
爱情就像农业
Love is a lot like farming,
你计划看看你是否希望它能成长
you plan to see if you hope it grows.
有时天气并不总是站在你这边
Sometimes the weather isn't always on your side.
只要有一点点运气
With a little bit of luck,
美丽的东西可以来自
something beautiful can come from,
这就是我想要找到的爱的类型
and that's the type of love that I want to find,
我来玩
and I'll play.
这段旅程将会让我到达那里
This journey is going to get me there.
我喜欢中西部和爱荷华州的一件事是我们有美丽的夏天 春天和文件
One thing I love about the Midwest and Iowa specifically is that we have beautiful summer's and springs and files,
如果你去冰岛的话 你的生活节奏会比较慢 如果你去冰岛的话 你的生活也会很美好
and you can kind of live a a slower pace and still have an awesome call your life if you go on Iceland,
这对我来说是非常重要的 并且能够找到在这个星球上珍爱的人必须与支持他们的穆斯林家庭相匹配
and it's extremely important to me and be able to find the one that cherishes around the planet has to match the Muslim family that support of them.
我有一些最好的朋友
There are some of my best friends.
我想她喜欢喝酒
I think she likes wine.
我的姐妹们都有很好的关系 我很欣赏
I sisters all have great relationships which I admire.
当我每天都去上厕所的时候
When I was gone for the bathroom every day.
你们呢
How about you guys?
我在看你们的节目
I'm watching what you guys out.
我看到我的姐妹和父母都有 我想要这真的很糟糕
I see with my sisters and parents have and I want to have that really bad.
他们可以向我反弹
They can rebound at me.
我们有很好的遗产
We have a pretty great heritage,
非常好的高质量的农民
really good highquality farmers.
我希望能继续前进 并希望将我的儿子或女儿的资金转移到右边
I'm looking to carry forward and hopefully pass along my son or daughter funds over here to the right.
这永远是我的职业生涯的起点
And this is always going to be where my career is from.
心是我想去的地方
The heart is where place that I want to be.
我热爱生命胜过一切
I love this life on the far more than anything,
但有一件事是很难找到的
but the one thing that it's really hard to find.
他的爱
his love.
这只是一点点
That's a little only out.
这里离文明20英里
Here were twenty miles from civilization,
基本上是跑到小的人群
basically running to the small population,
我认为这对数百人来说是很低的
I think it's low for hundreds.
早上
In the morning,
或者你在做我一直在找的那个人的工作
or else you're doing the job I've been looking for a long time for that person.
那是我生命中的伴侣
That's my partner in life,
那是我最好的朋友
that is my best friend.
我真的做对了
I was really gotten right.
是的
Yeah,
这个岛北部的穆斯林
the Muslims of the north of the island.
我认为做一个早期的否认会有点困难
I think it's going to be a little tough to do an early denial.
仅仅是不够
Just aren't enough.
长期以来 女性并没有得到它
Women long years didn't get it.
他在那里的农场没有得到它
His farm up there didn't get it.
我住在阿林顿
I stayed in Arlington.
利用这个机会
Take this opportunity of these an expenditure,
对我来说 这需要一辈子的时间
and it would take a lifetime to me.
二十五个女人 如果我现在要去三七十个正式的 那是两年前的一半
twenty five women if I was going to go now three seventy official half of what it was two years ago.
这是找到爱的最好方式
This is the best way to find love,
我等不及了
and I can't wait.
我非常认真地对待这件事
I am taking this really seriously.
我正在和托尼干我的屁股
I'm working my ass off of Tony.
你必须在工厂里做一个月的好朋友 而不幸的是 你要出来训练 做一些事情
You've got to be good friends with a month in the factory and misfortune out to do having come out and training do things.
一切都是为了你
It's all for you,
女士们喜欢现在还不算太晚
Ladies like it's not too late,
你可以改变你的想法
you can change your mind.
如果你真的想要一个来自阿灵顿的农民 我不会生气
I won't be upset if you really want a farmer from Arlington,
爱荷华州
Iowa,
成为下一批
being the next batch.
所以这将是我第一次错过收获
So this would be the first time that I've missed its harvest.
我在这里有很多责任
I've got a lot of responsibility here,
人们视我为领袖
and people looked to me as a leader.
在一个开车的人身上
in a person who drives things.
为了找到我的生命 我把所有重要的事情都抛在脑后
I am leaving behind everything that is important in order to find my life.
现在对我来说没有什么比这更重要的了
There's really nothing more important to me right now.
发射
Emitting.
真正的灵魂伴侣
True soul mate.
我很高兴能找到那个特别的人
And I'm just totally excited to find that special someone.
我想我不会在他们的头脑之前告诉我的鸡
I don't think I'm telling my chickens before their heads,
但我真的相信 当我等不及的时候 我可以在这段旅程中找到我的梦中情人
but I really do believe that I can find the woman of my dreams on this journey when I can't wait.
在一年中非常关键的时候 我们正处于丰收的季节 为了抑制自行车的存在 我在阿林顿的时候就不那么孤独了
Farming operations during a very critical time of the year when we're right in the middle of harvest to stifle bike held things are to me the less lonely in Arlington.
我不想吹这张寻找爱情的照片
I don't want to blow this shot of finding love.
这对我来说是一个很大的机会
This is a big opportunity for me.
我会发现我的妻子想要感谢每个人的支持 并帮助他们让你感到骄傲
I will find my wife want to thank everyone for their support and help them to make you proud.
作为美国的下一个信息
As America's next message.
第一次见到他的女人是令人兴奋的开始
First meets his women is the exciting beginning.
但首先
but first,
我们在红地毯上
we're here on the red carpet.
我在Geode和一个新生女婴身上注射了一根导管
What an amazing atmosphere that I shot a catheter here Geode and a new baby girl,
安第斯山的乔什
Andean Josh,
很多人
and many,
还有很多你的单身汉最爱我看到尼基
many more of your bachelor favourites I see Nicky well,
在最近和一个爸爸分手的时候 我要和她谈谈 这个问题真的和他在节目中一样糟糕
I'm going to talk to her up at the recent break up with one Papa was one problem really as bad as he was on the show.
当我们回来的时候 我们会发现更多的东西
We're going to find all that out more when we come back.
住在好莱坞参加单身首映
live here in Hollywood for the bachelor premiere.
我在这里
I'm here.
当单身汉们开始寻找爱情的时候
When the bachelors journey to find Love begins.
泄漏
Leaks,
我从来没见过这么漂亮的女人
the women I've never seen something beautiful in them.
这和你以前从未见过的完全不同
It's nothing like you've never seen before.
它是那么多东西
It's so much stuff.
然后这是一个没有其他人的聚会
And then it's a party like no other.
会有很长的一段时间
There's going to be a long.
我能看到人们眼中的恐惧
I could see the fear in people's eyes.
女孩们
girls.
他们根本没有和克里斯谈过
they haven't talked to chris' at all.
有什么恐慌吗
Is there any panic?
等等
Wait,
为什么所有的赌注都没了
why all bets are off?
这就像没有公牛整天都在 如果你想和我去年的一个导游谈谈
It's like there's no bulls all day went in for if you want to talk to me last year of a guide,
我喜欢这个
I like this at all.
如果你把他们从我身边带走 我在这里已经超过一年了
if you take them away from me and I've been here longer than a year.
这就够了
That's enough.
然后有些事情变得非常糟糕
And then something goes terribly wrong.
在玫瑰仪式上
At the rose ceremony.
一切都变得更加激烈
everything got so much more intense.
单身汉生活的时候 一切都要来了
It's all coming up when the Bachelors live.
季首播集继续
Season premiere continues.
在红毯上
To the bachelor red carpet,
我们今晚在好莱坞还活着
we are alive here in Hollywood tonight.
你最喜欢的单身汉们都在这里为新一季的单身汉们的生活首映式做准备
And your favorite bachelor stars are all here getting ready for the exciting life premiere of the new season of the bachelor.
在事情真正开始之前
Before things really get started,
让我们来谈谈我们在这个节目中遇到的最受欢迎的一对
let's talk to one of the most beloved couples we have ever had on this show.
准备好
Get ready,
女士们 先生们
ladies and gentlemen,
子弹和凯瑟琳
shot and Catherine.
伙计们来了
Guys come on up.
这太疯狂了
This is insane,
很好
it's great,
我喜欢它
I love it.
当你去达拉斯的购物中心时 我想这就是你的感受
I assume this is what it's like for you when you go to the mall in Dallas.
是的
Yeah,
不完全是
not quite,
我的意思是
I mean,
这里有很多令人兴奋的地方
this is a lot of excitement here.
我们在红毯上的粉丝们
We're alive on the red carpet tons of fans here,
但我想知道的是你的生活
but what I want to know about is your life back,
还有达拉斯
and Dallas.
你知道 订婚和婚礼让人兴奋不已
You know there was the excitement around the engagement and the wedding.
但现在你只是一对老夫妻了
But now you're just an old married couple.
那么达拉斯的生活又如何呢
So how is life back in Dallas?
我们喜欢动物的生活
We like the animal life.
生活是美好的
Life is great.
很简单
It's simple,
你知道我们都在做我们的工作
you know we both do our jobs,
我们都在一起 花时间和对方 狗和家人在一起 我们都很爱
we both hang out and spend time with each other and the dogs and our family and we love.
这是一个无聊的新年
It is a boring like new years.
我们在大新闻里坐在沙发上
We were on the couch in the big news.
显然是新婚之夜
obviously was the wedding night,
但我觉得我的工作超出了这个范围
but I feel like work beyond that.
我们讨论过孩子
So have we talked about kids,
单身的婴儿
bachelor babies?
我们已经谈过了
We have talked about them.
是的
Yeah,
我是说在我们的雷达上 我们只是在享受彼此
I mean there on our radar were just enjoying each other,
肖恩喜欢说我们在练习
and Sean likes to say were practicing.
雷达有多大 它们在右边
How big is the radar is that they're on the right?
或者这是什么意思
Or what does it mean?
这是一个模糊的术语
It's kind of a vague term.
我不知道
I don't know,
也许是二千零一十六
maybe maybe two thousand and sixteen,
你会看到一个婴儿
you'll see a baby,
爸爸
Papa,
我不知道那可能不是最好的
I don't know that's probably not the best.
他知道这是怎么运作的
He knows how it works,
但确实如此
but it does.
你知道婴儿是从哪里来的吗
You know where babies come from?
我们要坐下来谈一谈
We're going to sit down and have the talk.
我要让你和我的儿子同时坐下来
I'll sit you and my son down at the same time.
我们会得到这个
we'll have this.
好的
okay.
你已经在克里斯的位置上了
You have been in chris's shoes.
显然
Obviously,
今晚是他生命中的一个大夜晚
tonight a big night in his life,
他可以永远改变他的生活
he could change his life forever.
你认为他脑子里想的是什么
What do you think is going through his mind?
现在
Right now?
那些豪华轿车就要来了
Is those limos are about to arrive.
你知道
You know,
对我来说 这完全是一片混乱 因为我想到了所有的可能性 可能会发生什么 我可能会经历什么
it was just complete chaos for me in my mind because I was thinking of all the possibilities and what might come and what I might experience,
我希望他能冷静下来 镇定下来 意识到这将影响他的生活
and I hope he's just able to kind of calm down and gather himself and realize that this is going to shape his life.
它可能会
It possibly could,
他需要单独观察每一个女孩
and he needs to look at every girl individually and kind of.
穿舞会礼服和其他所有的东西看过去
see past the mansion in the ball gowns and everything else.
看看那个女孩
And just look at the girl.
你知道
and you know,
我的希望是他找到了像我一样的第一个晚上的人
my my hope is that he finds someone like I did that first night.
这是一团模糊的旋风
It is a whirlwind in a bit of a blur,
但是 当你那天晚上在大厦前的时候 有那么一刻对你来说是很重要的吗
but is there a moment that stood out to you as you were there in front of the mansion that night?
我想在第一架豪华轿车停之前
I think before the first limo pulled up,
这是一个多么离奇的时刻 我不知道谁会站出来
it was such a surreal moment and I didn't know who was going to step out,
我只花了一秒钟
and I just took a second.
我深吸了一口气
I took a deep breath,
我低下头
I put my head down,
我快速地祈祷
said a quick prayer,
然后 夜幕降临
and then the night began,
剩下的都是模糊的
and the rest was a blur,
你的祈祷应验了
and your prayer was answered.
给我另一个好处
Give me the flip side of that.
因为他站在大厦前面
Because he's standing in front of the mansion.
他拥有他身后的单身汉的力量
He has the power of the bachelor behind him.
今晚来的这些女人是什么感觉
What's it like for these women arriving tonight?
我认为这是一种超级神经的折磨 你不知道你第一个晚上会和谁成为朋友 因为你不想独自坐在那里
I think it's just super nerve racking and you don't know who you're kind of going to befriend that first night because you don't want to sit around by yourself.
所以我很幸运地遇到了很多好女孩 享受了这个夜晚 这样就不会有太多的压力要和他见面
So I was lucky enough to meet a lot of good girls and enjoy the night so that there wasn't too much pressure on meeting him.
所以我认为这对我来说很好
So I think that that worked out well for me.
但我知道很多女孩会去喝酒以缓解紧张
But I know that a lot of girls are going to take to the alcohol to help release tension.
但我很高兴我没有那样做
But I'm glad I didn't do that.
今晚有一个特别的女孩
One girl in particular a little too much tonight.
稍后你会看到可怜的塔拉
You'll see a little bit later on poor Tara.
好了
All right,
你们被藏在里面
you guys are hidden inside,
但在你走之前
but before you go,
充分利用这个单身国家的优势
take advantage of this bachelor nation is here in full force.
他们爱你
They love you,
男人们对凯瑟琳大叫
guys shout at Catherine,
每个人
everybody.
尽情享受表演吧
Enjoy the show.
还有更多来自我们的红地毯
There is more to come from our live red carpet,
Joshmarkets和莱西
Josh markets and lacy.
他们都在这里
They're all here.
我们绝对准备好了真正的独家新闻
We are definitely ready to get the real scoop.
克里斯是我们第一次来这里的
Chris makes the women for the first time we are gonna be here.
我的一生
all my life.
我们的总理
Our premier,
我是这个单身汉的克里斯哈里森
I am Chris Harrison at this bachelor nation.
单身汉的家庭 我们在这个夏天爱上了单身汉
Bachelor family that we really fell in love with this summer as they fell in love on Bachelor.
在天堂市场和Lacey市场
In Paradise Markets and Lacey markets.
很高兴见到你们
Great to see you guys,
你看起来很漂亮
you look beautiful,
我想最大的问题是我们都看到你在这个夏天爱上了你
I guess the big question you know we all saw you fall in love this summer has a go at you.
伙计们
Guys are engaged,
但你还在热恋吗
but are you still just madly in love?
尽管如此
Still,
继续坚持下去
keep on keeping on.
是的
Yeah,
在我们的婚礼中 有很多工作要做
in the middle planning our wedding and it's a lot of work,
但是我试着给他们更多的输入就像我不能做的一样
but I'm trying to give them as much input as I can't do this one bug,
所以这意味着你什么都不做
so which which means you're doing nothing.
好的
OK,
让我问你
let me ask you,
你在湿角上做所有的工作
you're doing all the work on the wet angle.
我们什么时候能期待
When can we expect?
这给了我们一个将军
This gives us a general.
我们今年肯定在计划
We are definitely planning this year,
希望在夏天的时候
hopefully in the summer time.
我们现在正好是80岁和40岁
We're a little eighty and forty on the exact date right now,
但计划肯定是在过去 我只是给他们一个日期 他会在那里
but the planning is definitely in the past that I just give them a date in the time he'll be there.
但严肃地说 这几乎是一见钟情
but in all seriousness it was almost love at first sight,
因为你们是我的单身汉和天堂
for you guys are bachelor and paradise to me.
对我来说 这真是太棒了
It was amazing to watch for me.
你们俩互相攻击
You guys were struck with each other,
然后你就离开了 开始了自己的表演
and you just kind of went off and had your own show.
你觉得克里斯今晚能找到吗
Do you think Chris could find that tonight?
你知道
You know,
克里斯
Chris.
显然
Obviously,
当然
absolutely.
我想他一定很容易找到爱情
I think he can definitely find love easily.
他是一个像你一样的老男孩
He's a good old boy like you,
我知道
and I know,
他来自草根阶层 他的道德和价值观忠实于他
and he comes from grassroots and his morals and values stick true to him,
他长大了
what he grew up,
我是这样认为的 我认为人们在节目中看到的是他真实的作为一个我同意的人
and I was so I think exactly what people see on the show is a reflection of what he truly is as a man I agree,
你可能从远处了解克里斯
and you probably know Chris from afar.
或者你怎么看这个来自爱荷华的农民
Or what do you think of this farmer from Iowa,
我认为他处境艰难
I think he's in a tough spot.
三十个女孩是很多女孩
Thirty girls is a lot of girls.
那些女孩必须要有攻击性才能在那里找到自己的位置
Those girl's gotta be aggressive to get their spot in there with craft,
一种尴尬的财富
an embarrassment of riches.
感谢你们今晚能来到这里
You guys thank you for being here tonight.
我很高兴你做得很好
I'm so glad you are doing well.
我等不及今年夏天的婚礼了
I can't wait for the wedding this summer.
你们走进去
you guys head on inside.
我们一会儿会看到
We'll see in a bit.
几乎是时候 水晶就要走到那座著名的公寓 在单身汉公寓里去见那些女人
It's almost that time crystals is about to walk up that famous driveway at the bachelor mansion to meet the women,
但在一切开始之前
but before it all began.
让我们来仔细看看其中的一些
So let's take a closer look at some of the batch,
你要为他的心而竞争
the ruts you'll be vying for his heart.
在洛杉矶单身很奇怪
It's very strange being single in LA.
我是这个城市的冒险之人
I am the adventuring through the city.
独自一人
All alone,
我想念陪伴
I miss companionship.
在你的生活中有一个男人是不同的
It's different to have a man in your life,
我已经有很长一段时间没有这样的经历了三年了
and I haven't had that for a really long time spent like three years now.
我认为亲密关系是如此重要 我不想在我知道其他的部分之前开始接触物理部分
I think that intimacy is so important that I don't want to start tapping into the physical part until I know the other pieces.
这是我的最后一段感情吗
Are there my last relationship?
我们根本就没有性生活
We don't have sex at all.
这是一件很有趣的事情 因为我知道我对他的感觉
It was kind of an interesting thing because I knew exactly how I felt about him.
不是基于任何事情
not based on anything.
身体上的
Physical.
我是个很敏感的人
I'm a very touchy person,
我很有感觉
I'm a feeler for sure,
我真的很想念它
and I do miss that.
我心里已经准备好让别人知道真正的肉了
The ready in my heart to be open for someone to know the real meat.
我要去看这个节目
I'm going on the show to me,
克里斯
Chris,
他真是个好人
He's such a good guy.
它不可能是任何人
It couldn't be anybody.
是否只是
whether it's just,
是的
yeah,
我是100%一百零一
I'm one hundred percent one hundred and one hundred.
吉里安和二十五岁 我是一个全国性的新闻制作人 你失去了这个有趣的孩子
Gillian and twenty five and I'm a national news producer working you lose this fun kid.
你可以看到它在细节上添加了一些东西
You see that it added something to the detail.
我想你
I think you,
我把我的心投入到我所做的每一件事上
I put my heart into everything that I do.
我想他们还是水可以对付一个强壮的女人
I think they're still waters can handle a strong woman,
但我想有些人会被我吓倒
but I suppose some guys are intimidated by me.
我去到那里去训练
I go to the jam I'm there to train,
我爱重 我爱它
I loved heavy and I love it.
我认为 我知道我是一个有竞争力的人 而不是很多人
I think that less is more than a lot of guys that I know I'm a competitive person.
寻找爱情是一种竞争
Finding love is a competition,
但我对这个想法很开放
but I'm really open to the idea.
但她在任何地方都找不到爱
But she can't find love anywhere.
克里斯可能会完全问他们一个对我来说太棒了
Chris might be completely ask them a completely great for me.
如果他是一个很好的人 每个人都在追踪他
If he is this great guy that everyone for tracing to be watch out,
女孩们悲伤地对我们说
girls sadly to us.
我是Amanda
I'm Amanda,
我来自伊利诺伊州
I'm twenty four from Leaky held Illinois,
我是一名芭蕾舞老师
and I'm a ballet instructor.
我从三岁起就想成为一名女士和服务人员
I want to be a lady and service since I was three.
我已经跳了二十年了
So I've been dancing for about twenty years now.
当我十六岁左右的时候 我开始教我的一些事实
an air of facts I started teaching when I was about sixteen nice and fluid trace the room,
我非常喜欢它和玩具
I absolutely love it and toys.
我可以吃点东西吗
Can I take some crazy?
我现在和我妈妈住在一起
I'm currently at home living with my mom,
我不喜欢付账单 也不做饭
I like not paying bills and I don't cook,
我不喜欢打扫卫生 所以我不喜欢这些东西
and I don't like cleaning so its great amount as those things.
但是我妈妈
But my mom,
他说
he said,
如果你有智慧
If you bears an intelligent,
你不是
you are not.
我很想找到爱
I would love to find love,
我觉得我已经准备好了
and I feel like I'm really ready for it.
你准备好生孩子了吗
Are you ready to make a baby?
我想我们都是对的
I think we are all right.
假设我想要我
Let's just say I want me,
我二十九岁
I am twenty nine.
我住在芝加哥
I live in Chicago,
伊利诺斯州和生育护士M
Illinois and M of fertility nurse.
这是我要教你们的注射
Here are the injections that I'm going to teach you about.
我遇到了一些夫妻 他们正在为各种原因而苦苦挣扎 原因可能是阻止他们生孩子的原因都是为了进行基因测试
I meet with couples that are struggling for whatever the reason may be that is preventing them from having children were all set to do genetic testing.
棒极了
Awesome,
他是对的
He's right.
我最喜欢的是生育神经 那就是完成一个人的家庭
The thing I love the most about being a fertility nerves is completing some one's family.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是世界上最好的感觉之一
It is one of the best feelings in the world,
但与此同时
but at the same time,
每天我都会想起一些我想念的东西
every day I am reminded of something that I'm missing.
我不知道我在哪里不意味着在芝加哥的正确的人
I have no idea where I'm not meaning the right guys in Chicago.
只是
It's just,
你知道
you know,
有时候 失去男孩只是不想安定下来 让你的爸爸变脆
sometimes losing boys just do not want to settle down to crisp your Daddy.
哦
Oh,
是的
yeah,
哦
oh,
是的
yes,
你兴奋吗
are you excited?
我认为媒体只是他朋友的一面镜子
I think press is just a mirror of his friends.
我想你刚才说玉米是你最喜欢的食物
I think you just said that corn was your favorite food.
看
Look,
你在舔嘴唇
you're licking your lips.
我可以帮忙做一些猪和牛
I could help with making some pigs and cows,
所有的爵士乐
and all that jazz,
你知道
you know,
我知道怎么做
I know how to do it,
所以我马上就到那里 把我的手弄脏
so I'll get right out there and get my hands dirty.
没问题
No problem.
当他还是麦肯齐的时候
When he was Mackenzie,
实际上 我已经有了一个非常特别的人 他的名字
and I actually already have a very special man in my life and his name,
他的尾巴
his tail.
老实说
Honestly,
一个孩子给你带来的快乐和幸福比我经历过的任何事情都要多
a kid brings you weigh more joy and happiness than anything I've ever experienced myself.
我喜欢和他出去玩 而不是出去玩 或者和我的朋友出去玩
I enjoy hanging out with him more than I do like going out or hanging out with my friends.
我和我儿子玩得更开心
I have way more fun with my son.
他有一张新面孔 每次他们失败 看着我 他就会这样做
He has this new face that he does that every time they failed and a look at me.
克里斯
Chris,
我认为它很高 你需要把它打开
I think it's high and you need to turn it.
长大了
Grown up.
这就是我想要的
That is what I want,
像男人一样
like a man,
克里斯是所有这些东西 就像它是完美的
and Chris is all those things one like it was perfect.
我有一盏小灯吗
Do I have a little lamp?
从飞行甲板上看 下午好吗
What looks good afternoon from the flight deck?
我们今天欢迎你的到来
We'd like to welcome you aboard today.
我叫阿丽莎 二十四岁
My name is Alyssa and Twenty Four.
我来自新泽西州
and I'm from New Jersey.
我是一名空姐
I'm a flight attendant.
早上好
Good morning.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
这架飞机禁止吸烟
smoking is prohibited on this aircraft.
除非你是在吸烟
Unless you're smoking hot hatreds,
我很兴奋 他创造了真正的兴趣
I'm so excited that he creates using through genuine interest.
加糖似乎是一个很有思想的人
sweetened seems like a really thoughtful person.
如果你有兴趣继续这段旅程去寻找爱情 玫瑰可能会被分发出去
Roses may be handed out if you're interested in continuing this journey to find love.
我觉得爱情就像飞翔一样
I think that love can feel a lot like flying,
你知道
you know,
因为当你离开的时候
because when you're off,
你走了
you're off,
然后你感觉很神奇 你感觉自己就像是在云端翱翔 在世界的顶端
then you feel amazing and you feel like you're just kind of soaring through the clouds and year on top of the world,
作为一个提醒
and just as a reminder,
女孩们
girls.
如果你不是出于正当的理由
if you aren't here for the right reasons,
离你最近的出口
your nearest exit,
也许在你身后的窗户里
maybe in the window behind you.
我很想飞到夕阳下
I would love to fly off into the sunset,
有了网格
with grids.
所以 非常感谢你选择了单身的空气 我们期待着在另一个航班上再次见到你
So thank you so much for choosing bachelor air and we look forward to seeing you again on another flight.
是吗
The?
我的名字是切尔西
My name is Chelsea.
我住在奥斯汀
I live in Austin,
德克萨斯
Texas,
我是学校辅导员
and I was school counselor.
这对我来说是有益的 我可以为那些刚刚开始生活的人做出贡献
That's rewarding to me that I get to contribute to people whose lives are just starting in a way.
你紧张吗
Are you nervous,
孤独的职业
lonely professionally,
我感觉自己就像我想要的那样
I feel like I am where I want to be,
但在我的生活中 还有其他一些地方让我觉得自己处于一种不确定的状态
but there are other places in my life where I feel like I'm in a state of limbo.
我做了一年零四个月的寡妇 我们计划买一套房子 安定下来 组建一个家庭
I've been a widow for a year and four months we were making plans to buy a house and settle down and have a family.
当他在一个美丽的日子里走路去上班的时候 所有的这些都被拿走了
And then all of that was taken away when he was walking to work on a beautiful day,
他的心跳停止了
and his heart stops.
我
And I.
它只是被淹没了
It was just overwhelmed and.
我是
I am.
我会醒过来 我知道我有一个选择
I would wake up and I knew I had a choice.
我可以躺在床上 生闷气 犯罪 或者我可以起床去上班 然后回来
I could stay in bed and sulk and crime or I could get up and go to work and give back.
即使我失去了我生命中的挚爱
Even though I lost a huge love in my life,
我相信灵魂伴侣是存在的 你可以遇见更多的灵魂伴侣
I believe that soulmates exist and that you can meet many more than one soulmate.
我最大的希望就是爱上一个人
My greatest hope is to fall in love with a person.
他是否爱上了我
Has him fall in love with me?
我走进了未知的世界
I'm walking into the unknown.
我冒着风险 我把自己放在这条线上
I'm taking the risk I'm putting myself on the line,
但实际上
but actually,
我真的很兴奋
I'm really excited about it.
下一个
Up next.
水晶之旅寻找爱生爱
Crystals journey to find love begets love,
这并不是人们所期望的
and it's not anything like anyone expected.
看看奥巴马
Look at Obamas,
克里斯死了
Chris is dead.
性感是微笑
Sexy is smile.
这是任何工作
It's just any job.
这是一个令人震惊的鸡尾酒会
And then it's a shocking cocktail party.
其中一个
One of them.
这就把女孩们推到她们还没和克里斯谈过的女孩身上
That pushes the girls over the girls they haven't talked to chris' at all.
然后你可能在他离开之前 让你仍然是我最好的方式
Then you might even before he was off to have you got still usually the best way for me,
我一直在
and I've been.
你在骗我
You're lying to me.
这太乱了
This is so messed up.
玫瑰仪式出了什么问题
What goes wrong at the rose ceremony?
看看那些令人兴奋的生活总理是什么时候还在继续的
Find out when the exciting life premier of the bets were continues.
哦
Oh,
是的
yeah,
不要你的钱
don't your money.
回到单身汉的红地毯上
Back to the red carpet of the bachelor,
今晚 我们的现场直播派对已经正式开始了
Premier Bachelor nation has shown up in full force tonight for our live viewing Party.
今晚在这里的一场爆炸
A blast to be here tonight,
我希望你能得到他的一部分
I hope you get the part of him.
我希望你在家里准备好自己的观影会
I hope you get ready for your own viewing parties at home.
现在加入我的是新婚夫妇
joining me now are newly engaged couple.
把它拿出来做真正的事情
Bring it up for the real thing.
看起来不错
Look good.
这有多棒
How awesome is this?
他试着去
He tried to.
我和肖恩和凯瑟琳在开玩笑
I was joking around with Sean and Kathryn.
但是你知道
But you know,
当你们出去的时候
when you guys go out.
我打赌它有点像这样
I bet it's a little bit like this,
在那里 人们都很兴奋地看到你 看到你现在的爱
where people are just so excited to see you and to see this love between you now.
相当大
Quite this big.
我不知道我们能否在日常生活中管理它
I don't know if we can manage its on an everyday basis,
但这很有趣
but it's fun,
你知道
you know,
我们看到很多人都非常支持
we've actually seen a lot of people that are just super supportive,
这总是很美好的
which is always nice to see,
我的意思是
I mean,
如果我们要去杂货店 你会觉得我们很高兴
if we're going to the grocery store and you will be like we're so happy.
你选择了他
You chose him,
这让我感觉很好
and that just makes me feel good.
我不去购物我们很多人都很开心
I don't make shopping a lot of us who was happy,
你真的选择了他们
you chose them really anybody.
让我们谈谈
Let's talk,
婚礼
wedding.
显然
Obviously,
我们仍然对订婚感到兴奋
we're still excited about the engagement,
但我们都开始谈论更多关于婚礼的事情
but we all started talking more about a wedding at a time time.
是的
Yeah,
我们只是在等待
we're just waiting.
我们期待着安定下来
We're looking forward to just settling down,
放松一下 然后和对方在一起玩
just relax and then having some fun with each other.
好消息是我们有你知道的
and the good news is we have you know.
我只是跟莱西和市场的婚礼说 在几周的时间里 克里斯和克里斯都结婚了 所以你们要排队等着你们去参加舞会
I just talk to Lacey and markets wedding coming up Dasn't Chris in a couple of weeks getting married so you guys just get in the queue you're going to get on the ball.
我觉得一旦你开始计划
I feel like once you start planning,
虽然没有停止
though there's no stopping,
所以我必须做好准备 他准备好去品尝所有的食物 喝下所有的酒
so I've got to really be ready to plan and he's going to really be ready to taste all the food and drink all the wine,
在他们这样做之前
and until they do,
你喝一点酒来品尝你知道的食物
you drink a little wine to taste the food you know,
我可以吃
I can eat.
在你这个季节 有一个来自爱荷华州的甜农
So there was this sweet farmer from Iowa on your season,
显然不适合你
obviously not right for you.
但是他被抛入了美国的意识中
But he was thrown into the consciousness of America,
每个人都爱上了这个人
and everybody has fallen in love with this guy.
很明显他是我们的单身汉
Obviously he's our bachelor.
关于克里斯 你能告诉我们什么 也许是单身汉国家不知道
What can you tell us about Chris that maybe bachelor nation doesn't know,
我的意思是
I mean,
我认为分页看到了克里斯的很多人
I think Pagination saw a lot of who Chris was,
这是最好的部分
which is the best part about it,
就像你看到的克里斯 他是谁
like what you saw of Chris was was who he is.
他是个好人
He's a nice guy.
他是一个总是走在大街上的人
He's a guy that takes the high road always,
我说他对我很好 当他笑的时候 当他到达那里的时候
I said he was as kind to me when he laughed as he was when he got there,
我很高兴人们看到他没有像他展示的那样有很多秘密
and I'm glad that people saw that there is not really a whole lot of secrets to him like he showed it.
这对Josh来说很有趣因为我知道他是一个多么好的人
and it's fun for Josh tonight because I know what a nice guy he's been.
还有
Also,
乔什和他是好朋友
Josh was good friends with him,
所以我觉得我们俩都很开心看到他是一个多么伟大的人 并且能够让他一起为他加油
so I think it's just been fun for both of us to see what a great guy he is and to be able to to kind of cheer him on together.
所以我想说他是你的一个儿子
so I was going to say he's one of your boys.
好的
OK.
剧透警告今晚有三十个女人
Spoiler alert Theres thirty women tonight.
你觉得你的投篮怎么样
so how do you think your shot?
你害羞吗
you're shy?
我总是要处理好你要杀了它
I was always going to handle that you're going to kill it.
然后我们会在一个系统中喝一些好的饮料会有很多乐趣
Then we're going to have some good drinks in a system is going to have a lot of fun.
你将需要2到30个女孩
It's going to be you're going to need two and thirty girls,
女孩们
girls.
我想我们总共有二十七个
I think we had twenty seven over all,
尽管如此
though,
你认为他会找到他应得的爱吗
do you think he's going to find love he deserved.
是的
Yeah,
我认为他是那种已经准备好了的人
I think he's the type of person that's ready for it.
他想知道他是否还没准备好
And he wondered if he wasn't ready,
他告诉我们 我们在节目开始前和他谈过
and he told us that we talked him before the show,
我们都知道他已经准备好了
and we just both knew that he was ready for this.
所以我肯定他会找到的
so I definitely think he's going to find it.
你认为你会发现那个特别的人也可以带回来
You think you'll find that special someone who can take back too.
我的意思是
I mean,
我认为这将是一个要求
I think that's going to be a requirement.
你知道
you know.
他毫不犹豫地说 这就是他的生活所在
he makes no bones about the fact that that's where his life is,
这很好
and it's good.
他对此非常关注
He's very up front about it,
所以我认为他会找到一个不介意成为爱荷华州的女孩 因为我的意思是 这很好
and so I think he's going to find a girl that doesnt mind being an Iowa because I mean it's great.
我去了那里
I went there,
我喜欢它
I loved it,
他喜欢那里
he loves it there,
所以我想你会在那里找到合适的女孩
so I think you'll find the right girl there.
我的意思是你不想去那里
I mean you don't want to go there,
但是在适当的情况下 有人去了那里
but someone well gone there under the right circumstances,
所以我想你会找到一个人
so I think you'll find someone.
我知道 这比让你们看起来漂亮的生活更有意义
I know that that's more than willing to make a life where you guys look beautiful.
我很高兴你的生活一切顺利
I'm glad everything is going well in your lives.
持续的成功
Continued success,
我们将在印度国内看到
and we'll see inside India,
Josh
Josh,
每个人
everybody.
再来一个人
Coming up next one more person,
我们今晚一定要和你谈谈
we definitely need to talk to you tonight.
尼基在这里 现在是时候了解她和胡安巴勃罗的单身粉丝分手的真实故事了
Nikki is here and it is time to get the real story about her breakup with Juan Pablo bachelor fans.
他们真的不喜欢这个家伙
They really didn't like this guy.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
我们来看看尼基 Ssl
Let's say what Nicky Ssl,
尽管接下来会发生
though it's all coming up next.
为什么
Why,
这是我们的医生给我的吗
here from our doctor for me?
Mitre
Mitre.
啊
Ah.
离开
Coming off.
所以我自己
So myself.
哦
Oh,
我的上帝
my God,
我想要建立
I want to set up,
让游戏开始吧
let the games begin,
把古怪的人带来
bring on the weirdos,
然后是鸡尾酒会让每个人都大吃一惊
and then it's a cocktail party that will surprise everyone.
为什么不呢
Why not?
多花点时间
Spend a little bit more aggressive.
我觉得自己很强大
I feel powerful.
后来这是一个令人震惊的玫瑰仪式
And later it's a shocking rose ceremony,
没有其他的
like no other.
一切都变得更加激烈
Everything got so much more intense.
我不知道这是100%对你来说
I had no idea that this would go like this is a hundred percent up to you.
这一切都是在单身汉的精彩的谎言首映式上出现的
It's all coming up on the exciting lie premiere of the bachelor.
优柔寡断
Vacillation.
我坠入了爱河
I fell in love.
一种特殊的时尚
A special fashion.
在好莱坞 看老板看不见单身汉
Viewing the owner sees no the bachelor here in Hollywood,
但首先 我有一个核心 我们最近的一批夫妻要么已经结婚 要么即将成为约翰和凯瑟琳结婚
but first I had a core of our most recent batch of couples are either married or are about to be John and Katharine married.
我们听说了约书亚的婚礼计划
We heard about any Joshua's wedding plans,
我们要祝贺死亡和媒体 他们将会在短短几周内交换他们的誓言
and we'd like to congratulate deaths and press who will be exchanging their vows and just a short couple of weeks.
然后
So then,
胡安-巴勃罗和尼基之间发生了什么
what happened between Juan Pablo and Nicky?
嗯
Well,
你回答我们所有的问题
you to answer all of our questions.
尼基
Nicky.
你好吗
How are you doing?
我真的做得很好
I'm actually doing really great.
是的
Yeah,
我真的很开心
I'm really happy.
嗯
Well,
显然 每个人都仍然深爱着你
apparently everyone is still very much in love with you.
让我们回到上次你和我在这幢大楼里的最后一排特别的时候
Let's go back to the last time you and I were in this very building the after the final row special.
对我们中的任何一个人来说 这都不是最好的时刻
It wasn't the best moment really for either one of us.
带我回到你那天晚上的想法
Take me back in what you were thinking that night.
很明显 你把所有的情绪都给了你
Obviously you kind of gave all of your emotions.
胡安-巴勃罗那天晚上并没有犯什么错
And then Juan Pablo didn't what went wrong that night.
在你的眼中
In your in your eyes,
我是说
I mean.
首先
First of all,
在公众的眼里 很难有一段感情
it's really hard to have a relationship that's like seen in the public eye,
我觉得我很乐意表达我的感受
and I feel like I was comfortable with expressing my feelings,
他不是
and he wasn't,
我知道在那天晚上 你知道
and I knew that going into that night and you know,
这和他的女朋友很好
and that's fine as his girlfriend,
我想要尊重这一点 因为我要站在我的男人身边
I wanted to respect that because I was going to stand by my man.
你知道
You know,
它将会是100%
with it going to be one hundred percent,
我的选择
my choice.
不
No,
但我的意思是 我关心他 我想成为一个好女友 我想和她的男人站在一起
but I mean I cared about him and I wanted to be a good girlfriend and I wanted to stand by her man.
这就是我那天晚上选择做的事情
And so that's what I chose to do that night.
这是一种感觉
There was just this sense,
通常当我们完成一场演出的时候
usually when we finish a show,
特别是当我们有几个他们的时候
especially when we have a couple of theirs.
这是一种强烈的快乐感 我们都出去庆祝一下
Is this overwhelming sense of joy and we all go out and celebrate it.
出于某种原因
For some reason,
这是一种敌意
there was just this kind of animosity.
就像你们在对抗世界
it was like you guys against the world,
这必须很艰难
and that had to be tough,
我敢肯定这是你不想要的
and I'm sure it's something you didn't want.
我也不想要
I didn't want it either.
我的意思是
I mean,
没有人会为你在节目中发生的事情做好准备 就像在聚光灯下一样
No one prepares you for what's going to happen on the show and like it like being in the spotlight,
但你知道 那晚我确实觉得这样做会更容易些
but you know that night I do feel like it could have been easier,
但是我在晚上的时候感到不开心
but I didn't feel happy at the end of the night.
我只是
I just,
我想让所有人都为我高兴
I wanted I wanted everyone else to be happy for me,
我觉得这是被误解了
and I felt like it was misunderstood,
它被误解有很多原因
and it was misunderstood for a lot of reasons.
它被误解了 因为我们不能以一种我想要表达的方式来表达我们自己
It was misunderstood because we weren't able to express ourselves mostly him in a way that I wanted it to be expressed.
我想让每个人都为我高兴
I wanted everyone to be happy for me,
但你们确实做了一件事
but you guys did make a go of it.
你和你的男人站在一起 你们最近也有过一段恋情
You stood by your man and you guys had a relationship recently.
显然
Obviously,
我们已经知道你已经分手了
we've read that you've broken up.
发生了什么
What happened?
这不是因为两边都缺少火车
It's not from a lack of train on either side.
你知道
You know,
我非常努力 他努力地去做
I tried really hard and he tried hard to.
只是
It's just,
我是堪萨斯城的一名护士
I'm a nurse in Kansas City,
他住在迈阿密
and he lives in Miami,
他就像在娱乐行业 这是他的工作
and he's like in the entertainment industry and that's his job,
这就是他的生活方式
and that's his lifestyle,
我只是
and I just.
这对我来说真的很难适应
It was really hard for me to fit into that.
在一天结束的时候 我们给了它一个机会
and at the end of the day we gave it a go.
但我们是太不同的人 你确实做了一件事
But we're just too different people and you did make a go of it.
事实上
In fact,
甚至在一种谣言开始流传之后
even after a kind of rumors had started swirling about,
你分手了
you're breaking up,
你付出了努力 你去了迈阿密 给了它最后的努力
you made the effort and you went to Miami to just give it one last ditch effort.
是的
Yeah,
我绝对不会放弃 因为我不是一个放弃的人
absolutely like I wasn't going to quit like I'm not a quitter.
所以我尝试了所有的东西
And so I tried everything,
我知道他试过
and I know he tried to.
我的意思是 这不仅仅是单方面的事情
I mean it wasn't just a one sided thing,
但就像在一天结束的时候
but like at the end of the day,
我们有不同的侧重点
we have different priorities.
我们有不同的生活方式 这就是它的样子
we have different lifestyles and it just it is what it is like it,
我们尝试过 我们的现实生活不像电视上的尝试
we try and we real life tried not just like TV tried,
但我的意思是 我同意这一点
But I mean in and I agree with that,
我知道 因为你要做的一件容易的事就是离开 因为艰难的事情是留下来
I know because the easy thing for you to do would have been to walk away because the tough thing was to stay,
但是你说你有不同的优先级
but you said you have different priorities,
我知道你很友善
and I know youre being nice.
但是你有优先考虑吗
But were you ever that priority?
你是否觉得我所知道的最重要的事
Did you feel like the priority I know,
比如你去迈阿密的时候
like when you went to Miami,
当你在那个时候没有得到关注的时候 事情有点不太好
Things were a little off putting when you didn't get that attention in that time,
我的意思是 我知道我知道我永远不会成为第一要务 就像他有一个女儿一样
I mean like I knew I knew I was never going to be the number one priority like he has a daughter.
但我的意思是 在第七优先级中 第二优先级是有区别的
but I mean there's a difference between being like the second priority in the seventh priority.
我的意思是
So I mean.
你知道
You know,
只是我们只是不同的人有不同的东西他认为是可以的 我不认为他们是可以的
it's just that we're just different people and there's different things that he thinks are OK and I don't think they're okay.
我们对他的看法从来都是不一致的
And we just never saw eye to eye on him.
我们从来没有
and we just never.
我们会对它的看法一致
We're going to see eye to eye on it,
所以你想要它
so you want it.
我的意思是显然有一个女儿和一个家庭是第一位的
I mean obviously has a daughter and family comes first.
但就像你说的 你应该就在那后面
but like you said you should be right behind that.
你是否觉得他对聚光灯的爱 在公众的眼中 成为其中的一部分
And did you feel like his love of the limelight and in the public eye and being a part of that,
羔羊的生活方式使他付出了代价 得到了他最好的
the lamb lifestyle kind of took took its toll and got the best of him.
在某些方面
In some ways.
他喜欢成为娱乐行业的一员
He loves being part of the entertainment industry,
不管他是不是在聚光灯下
whether he's in the spotlight or not.
这是我不知道的
That's something I don't really,
我真的不知道 因为我离它太远了
I don't really know because I am so far removed from it.
我觉得当我在家的时候 我觉得这根本不是我的首要任务
I feel like when I'm at home like it's just it's not a priority for me at all,
所以我们很难聚在一起 因为我从来没有见过他的样子
and so it's really hard for us to get together on that because I never saw it the way he saw it,
我做到了
I did it,
我想打开那些门
I guess to open up those doors.
你是否觉得他真的爱上了你
Did you feel like he was ever really just in love with you,
是关于你们和你们这段关系的吗
that it was about you and you guys in this relationship?
是的
Yes,
有一段时间 我确实觉得他和我在一起
there was a while where I did feel like he was totally a lot with me.
是不是太晚了
Was it too late?
我们等着
We'll wait.
这是怎么回事
Is that what happened?
它实在是太少了
It was just too little,
太晚了
too late.
我只是
I just,
我想
I think,
在这一点上
at that point,
就像我刚刚得出的结论 我们是不同的人 我们永远不会在同一页上 而不是我有任何强烈的感情 在这种情况下我不能为他说话
like I had just come to the conclusion that like we're different people and we're never going to be on the same page and not that I have any hard feelings and I can't speak for him in the situation.
但我知道
But I just knew that,
就像我的生活方式永远无法融入他的生活
like my lifestyle was never going to fit in with his.
显然
Obviously,
当事情变糟的时候 你会感到愤怒
you have felt the wrath of what you know when things went bad.
我知道你也有很多热量
I know you've got a lot of heat as well.
你觉得怎么样
What was that like for you?
这是我遇到过的最困难的事情之一
That was one of the hardest things I've ever had to deal with.
我觉得我还没准备好
I feel like I wasn't prepared for it,
就像每个人说的
like everyone says,
哦
Oh,
是的
yes,
你签了名
you signed up for it,
是的
and yes,
我做到了
I did.
你是对的
You're right,
我做到了
I did,
但是人们对我说的那些伤人的话 没有人能帮你做好准备
but the hurtful things that people said to me like it just no one can prepare you for that.
这对我来说真的很难 我真的很幸运他能在那里支持我
and it was really hard for me and I'm really lucky that he was there to support me through that.
因为
because.
我只是
I just,
我处理得不好
I didn't handle it well,
直到今天 我仍然觉得我在挣扎
and I still feel like I struggle with it to this day.
我是说我是人类
I mean I'm human,
我犯了错误 我还没有准备好让我的生活和我的爱情生活在国家电视台上播出
I make mistakes and I wasn't ready for my life and my love life to be broadcast on national television.
你后悔什么吗
Do you regret anything?
如果是这样
And if so,
你最后悔的是什么
what do you regret the most?
你知道
You know,
我不后悔任何事情 因为我觉得自己成长得像一个人
I don't regret anything because I feel like I've grown so much as a person,
我真的很感激这次经历 因为我知道我是谁
and I am really grateful for the experience because I know who I am,
我知道我想要什么
and I know what I want,
我知道我不想要什么
and I know what I don't want,
你知道
and you know,
我只是
I just,
我真的很开心
I'm really happy.
我现在很开心
I'm happy now,
我爱我的生活
and I love my life.
很多人在看你 知道我们在这里
A lot of people watching you know that night we were here.
我们准备扔一些东西 比如不做
we were ready to throw things like making no,
不要这样做
don't do this.
不要陷入这种关系
Don't get into this relationship.
你在胡安巴勃罗看到的是我们都这么做了因为我认为很多人认为这整件事是注定要失败的
So what did you see in Juan Pablo that we all did it because I think a lot of people thought that this whole thing was set for failure.
你知道
You know,
我们都想救你
we were all trying to save you.
好的
OK,
但是你去了
but you went.
所以
So.
在胡安巴勃罗 我们没有看到什么
What did we not see in Juan Pablo?
什么被误解了
What's misunderstood?
他是如此的带着你的真爱
He is so carry like you really does.
他很关心他的家庭
He cares so much about his family,
他很关心他的朋友们
and he cares so much about his friends,
他关心那些他信任的人
and he cares about people that he trusts,
他真的
and he really.
他是个好人
He's a good person.
我没有什么不好说的
I don't have anything bad to say I just.
这只是生活方式的不同
It's just a difference of lifestyles.
他很关心我
And he cared so much about me,
他关心我的家庭
and he cared about my family,
他真的是一个好人
and he really is a good person.
他现在真的是
He really is now.
他无法真正表达自己的情感 说
There was so much made of the fact that he could never really speak his emotions and say,
我爱你
I love you.
他有没有告诉过你他爱你
Did he ever tell you he loves you?
他做到了
He did absolutely.
我想我告诉过你我将会是决定什么时候够了
I think I told you like I'll be the one to decide when enough is enough,
我们之间的关系并没有结束 因为我们没有彼此相爱
and the relationship didn't end because we didn't love each other,
你知道
you know,
或者是因为缺乏沟通
or because of a lack of communication.
它只是结束了 因为生活方式的不同你知道有一点
it just ended because the difference of lifestyles and you know there is a point where,
就像我们说的
like we said,
我们像正常的关系一样爱着对方
we loved each other like a normal relationship,
你知道 这是一个不同的人 就像我希望人们能在路上知道的那样
and you know it just is a different person like I just wish that people can get to know in the way.
我只是感觉到了
I just get the sense that again,
它不会让你成为一个坏的男朋友或者不正确的人
it doesn't make you a bad person to be a bad boyfriend or not right,
我能感觉到你在寻找什么
and I get the sense that what you're looking for,
有些人会更专注于你 让你成为优先考虑的人
someone who will be a little more dedicated a little more into you and make you a priority.
我觉得你从来没有觉得你是这段关系的优先级而打高尔夫球或参加派对总是有先例的
And I feel like you never felt like you were the priority in this relationship and that going golfing or going to parties are going always kind of took precedent.
对
Right,
他只是
he's just,
你知道 当你住在两个不同的地方 比如我住的地方 我想到的是这个城市
you know when it's hard when you live in two separate places like I living and I was thinking of the city.
他住在迈阿密
He lived in Miami,
所以他在迈阿密的生活对他来说是非常重要的
so his life in Miami was very much a priority for him.
你知道
And you know,
所以当我来的时候
so when I would come there,
我觉得我就像是被扔进了他的生活
I feel like I was just kind of like thrown into his life,
但话说回来
but then again,
当他来到秦城时
when he came to Qin the city,
他刚刚被扔进了我的生活
he was just thrown into my life.
所以这很难
So it's hard it was hard.
从一开始就不容易
it wasn't easy from the start.
嗯
Well,
我很高兴你来了
I'm glad you came here.
我很高兴你又回到了单身家庭
I'm glad you're back a part of the bachelor family.
我知道他的路很艰难
I know he's a tough road,
但我很高兴你今晚能来
but I am glad you're here tonight,
很高兴见到你
and it's great to see you.
尼基
Nicky,
每个人
everybody.
上来
Coming up,
大约是在那个时候 每个人都要搬进来 一份生动的报告即将开始
it's about that time everybody is about to move inside and a lively report is about to begin.
我们就会离开克里斯
We'll just moments away from Chris,
意思是天气
meaning the weather.
都被覆盖了
It's all covered.
对象
objects.
啊
Ah.
一个美好的夜晚
A great night,
我们又回到了哈里森市长的实验室
we've come back to the lab for mayor of the bachelor interest Harrison.
每个人都在自己的座位上坐着 而现在在家里的工作室里
Everyone has taken their seats while they are taking their seats now here in the studio at home,
酒已经倒了
the wine has been poured.
每个参加单身汉幻想联盟的人都填满了他们的括号
Everyone who's part of a bachelor fantasy league has filled out their brackets.
我希望这能带来好运
I hope good luck on that.
今晚大家感觉怎么样
How's everybody feeling so far tonight?
这是玻璃做的
This is made of glass.
你们都准备好参加这个单身汉聚会了吗
Are you all ready to get this Bachelor viewing party started.
嗯
Well,
猜猜看 克里斯
guess what Chris,
他寻找爱情的旅程现在开始了
His journey to find Love begins right now.
到洛杉矶来
To be here in LA.
在这批材料中
In the batch of material,
一些身体上的经历
some out of body experiences.
他比我今晚的速度快得多
He's a lot faster pace than I like tonight.
这是一个完全不同的世界 在一平方英里的范围内 比我居住的整个殖民地的人都多
It's a whole different world this more people in a square mile than there is in the entire colony that I live.
我更不愿意在交通繁忙的市中心开车
I'll let alone driving downtown in traffic that's intimate,
但我愿意尽一切努力去寻找
but I'm willing to do whatever it takes to find,
爱和坠入爱河 把它带回我自己的眼睛
love and fall in love and bring it back to my own eyes.
如果它无处不在
If it did everywhere,
但这里呢
but here?
我已经脱离了我的联盟
I'm way out of my league here.
我正试着关掉最喜欢做的事情
I'm trying to close the favorite things to do.
中国说 我觉得这将是我想做下一件事的唯一原因 就像一种趋势
China says it feels like this is going to be just as much work as far as the only reason I want to do next pleasures like a trend,
七千
seven thousand,
五个旺季
five close season,
戳戳和刺戳 而不是权利的趋势
poke and prod and less than rights trend.
在精神上和体力上都让人精疲力竭
It's a lot of work mentally emotionally and physically exhausting.
我们多么希望能像收割玉米一样把它藏起来 让他看到它或针
How young we wish that was as harvesting corn is putting the hidden it and let him see it or needles.
最后
Last.
我知道我这么做是有正当理由的
I know deep down that I am doing this for the right reasons,
是为了找到我的妻子
and it's to find my wife.
这就是我看到的全部目标
That's the whole goal I saw me.
我可以离开这里 盖住别人的手指
I can leave here covering around someone's finger.
这整个旅程将是值得的
This whole journey will be more than worth it.
我发现有人很兴奋能和真正的成年人打交道
I find somebody gets excited to deal with the real grownups.
农民
Farmers.
一年前的今天 我已经为艺术家们准备好了 因为他们从来没有想过要去做贝斯
A year ago today I was getting ready for artists never had even thought about even being on the bass,
REDD或者是有史以来最好的
REDD or being in the best ever.
现在 这将是最不可思议的经历
and now it's going to be the most incredible experience.
我的整个人生
my entire life.
不久前还发生了一些非常美好的回忆
Have some really great memories happened here not too long ago.
我现在感到非常幸运 能够住在离引擎几百英尺远的地方 离所有的女士都很近
I feel very fortunate right now to be able to live hundreds of feet away from the engine really close to all the ladies.
我想花尽可能多的时间在这些可能的事情上 当他们觉得这是我能吃的东西
I want to spend as much time with one of those possible when they feel like it's what I can eat.
我将会有一点改变 让我住在离二十五个狂野女人的石头上
I'm going to be a bit of a change to be living in literally a stone's throw away from twenty five wild women.
有一件事我很担心它的意思是多重
One thing I'm worried about its meaning multiple,
真的很棒
really awesome,
他们将很难做出决定
and they'll have a tough time making a decision.
这可能是我最关心的问题
That's probably my biggest concern.
同样让人害怕的是 这个过程的一部分就是要让这些女人成为她们想要成为的人
It's also scary to know that part of this process is about putting these women that I am somebody they want to be.
我的一部分想知道谁想和一个来自阿林顿的农民约会
Part of me is wondering who wants to date a farmer from Arlington.
我要做我自己
I'm going to be myself.
我已经准备好开始这件事了
I am so ready to get this thing started.
你是一头牛
You're a cow.
克里斯仍然高高在上 第三个星云在今晚之后将会全部结束
Chris is still high and the third nebula after tonight's going to be all over when to go.
让我们做一个令人惊讶的家伙
Let's do is an amazing looking guy.
谁是那个热的农民
Who's that hot farmer.
我很兴奋 因为我真的很想了解他
And I'm excited because I really want to get to know him.
冒险
Adventure.
我不知道该期待些什么
The sponsor of the money that I have no idea what to expect,
我的意思是积极的感觉 即使是在我未来的妻子 仍然不能相信这对我有帮助
I mean active sense even in my future wife and still can't believe it's helped me,
但我准备好了
but I'm ready.
真不敢相信
Can't believe this.
克里斯死了
Chris is dead.
性感是微笑
Sexy is smile.
只是皮亚尼
It's just Piani.
一滴
droplet hah,
我要把它保存好
I'm just going to keep it all right.
这里也是西西里
So here we also Sicily.
是吗
The?
Do you?
好的
Okay.
所以你有很长一段时间
So you had a long time.
但是你知道
But you know,
我读得很漂亮
I read beautiful,
你见过类似的吗
So have you seen similar to here?
我一直在思考这个问题
I've been thinking about this now,
这段旅程需要多长时间 我所看到的关于你的简历的一切都很容易
how long a journey this is happening and everything I've seen about your resume is easily like,
我已经知道我喜欢你了
and I already know I like you,
不管怎样 我有一条腿 给你一些东西
so I have a leg up anyway and a little something for you,
你必须向我保证
and you have to promise me,
你会来找我的
you'll come find me.
还有缟玛瑙
And onyx.
自从我很快见到你 这些就太好了
These are so much since I see you soon.
不受英国的欢迎
Free from Britain.
好的
Okay,
就这样
with that.
会议或者是你认为你
The meeting or something that you think you,
我需要一个蓝色的
that I need to have a blue.
我听说过你的名字 真是太棒了
I've heard your name and it was amazing.
你看起来棒极了
You look awesome,
所以我从她上高中的时候就开始看这个节目了 说实话 在你们之前
so I have watched the show since she was in high school and to be honest Thursday Great Gods ahead of you,
但如果不是你 我就不会在这里
but I wouldn't be here if it was not you.
老实说
honestly,
我只是迫不及待地想和你说更多的信息
I just can't wait to talk to you more info.
我需要另一个
I need another.
好了
All right,
里面有些东西
something inside.
真的
Real,
我也很高兴见到你
so nice to meet you too.
你正在慢慢地为这次冒险加油吗
Are you rooting for this adventure slowly?
我很高兴和你在一起
I'm glad it's with you,
你知道
and you know,
我有点想起来了
I'm kind of seeing a bit of thinking.
我从豪华轿车里出来时非常紧张
I was so nervous getting out of the limo,
然后我走出去 看到你
and then I step out and I see you,
突然间我就不那么紧张了
and suddenly I'm not so nervous.
不仅仅是一个普通人
Something more than just a regular guy.
不要紧张
Don't be nervous.
我只是一个普通的女孩
I'm just a regular girl again.
带着校园的光辉
With the glow of the campus.
独自一人
Alone,
写博客
blogging.
再一次
Again,
这也是
this would be too.
你真了不起
You're amazing.
这通常是最后三十个人觉得太紧张了
This is often the last thirty feel too nervous.
是的
Yes,
不鼓励它的行动
discourages its move.
在12月
On Dec,
十对
ten right.
这并不是一件容易的事
It's not going to be easy.
就在一段时间之前
Take a while ago,
一张垫子或者你和艾希礼
a mat or you and Ashley.
我很高兴来到这里
I'm so happy to be here.
我没有分配给你 我现在也很紧张
I'm not allotted to you and I'm also really nervous right now.
我去过那里
I've been there.
是的
Yeah,
它会和他们一起玩
it is going to have fun with them,
我们都是这样
and we are all so.
我不会说自杀
I'm not going to say suicide.
我待会再跟你说
I'll talk to you later.
它将会看一看动物
It's going to take a look at animals.
哦
Oh,
我的上帝
my God.
是的
Yeah.
啊
Ah.
看起来很神奇的农民你知道并试着知道那是一个很好的老师只是为了让他们公平
Farmers who looks amazing is you know and trying to know that's a really good teacher just to get them into a fairly.
我的意思是
I mean,
只要说你可以去就好了
just say you're good to go.
今年
This year,
我们的输入
our input.
你我做得很好吗
Are you I'm doing very well?
你好吗
How are you?
我的名字已经恢复了一些 很高兴见到你
My name's have regained some of its very nice to meet you.
我有一份很有趣的工作 我很有人情味
I kind of have this really fun job where I so human.
统治者
Rulers,
是的
yeah,
所以我试着去想一些你知道的事情
and so I was trying to think of something that you know.
我会从心里得到你的
I would get you from the heart.
这是一件小礼物
So a little present.
我想是的
I think so.
我们两个人都有自己的语言 我很高兴能在这里找到男人和美女
Just the two of us have hangups and I'm really excited to get men and beautiful here.
我想要知道你在我们内心看到的
I want to get to know you see inside us.
不管怎样 我可能需要一个额外的努力
I might need an extra hard on the hand anyway.
啊
Ah.
你好吗
How are you?
我要
I'm gonna,
今天和你一起穿好鞋
Do a good boots with you today,
恐怖的星期一
Monday With terror,
很明显我不是穿着酒会礼服
I obviously are not in the cocktail dress,
因为这是我
because this is me,
你看起来棒极了
You look amazing and yeah,
我想你可以在这里做
I think you can do here.
意思是在里面
Means on the inside.
我喜欢你的风格
The town girls I like your style.
在三月
On March.
但我不认为我穿短裤的时候会穿牛仔衬衫 就像第一晚的第一印象
But I don't think I would ever dressed in shorts fan a cowboy shirts like the first night first impression.
也许再多一点 然后起草
maybe be a little more and draft.
阻止詹姆斯走错路
stop James on the wrong.
当我第一次带着牛仔靴走出家门的时候
When I first came out of the house with my cowboy boots,
我的牛仔短裤 我很高兴我绝对感觉不太合适
my jean shorts and I'm glad I definitely felt out of place totally judge.
你认为他们能判断他们想要什么
What do you think they can judge all they want.
但这是我
but this is me.
土生土长的小镇小女孩从小就以这种方式打猎
homegrown smalltown girl grew up hunting fish in this way.
上帝
God,
如果你能告诉你我的意思
if you would tell you who I mean,
每个人都必须为零
where everyone has to be zero,
只有经济
only economy,
这对我来说是一种安慰
it is kind of like a comfort for me,
我可以穿上一双细高跟鞋 把它们也画出来
I can throw on a pair of stilettoes and have drawn them as well.
我不在乎其他女孩对我有什么看法
I don't care what the other girls have the thing about me,
我更关注的是 因为惊讶
I'm more focus on because because of surprise,
我的上帝
my God,
我会尽我所能给枪留下第一印象
I would go out of my way to make a first impression of the gun.
嗨
Hi,
你怎么指出卑鄙的感谢
how are you pointing the sneaky thank you?
从字面上看 它只是一个来自秘鲁的线性关系
It literally just a linear from Peru.
说
To say,
关于酶的转化
regarding enzyme converts,
你在这里的一个好地方已经看到了它的距离
a good you're here has seen its distance.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
你好
Hello.
如果我想让你知道你可以带着这个国家的女孩离开我想要成为的那个女孩
Your back if I wanted to show you that you can take the girl in the country since the country out of the girl I wanted to be in this time,
没有这个过程 也没有其他人
there were none of the process or someone else.
这是三个方面
It's the three sides.
我更快乐
I'm happier,
克里斯说他看到了真实的我
says Chris got to see the real me.
是的
Yeah.
是吗
The?
你知道吗
You know?
警察
The cop.
这个
This?
是吗
The?
欧洲
Europe.
我不知道现在发生了什么 我坐在那里 期待着另一个女孩从豪华轿车里出来 而不是一个豪华轿车司机 走上前给我一张纸条
I have no idea what's going on right now and I'm sitting there expecting another girl to come out of the limo instead a limo driver and walks up and gives me a note.
好的
OK.
克里斯
Chris,
请离开豪华轿车 闭上你的眼睛
please turn away from the limo and close your eyes,
拥抱和亲吻
hugs and kisses.
是吗
The?
好的
Okay,
没有北京的迷幻药
no Peking LSD.
然后你真的想让美国和你的秘密仰慕者一起
then you really want America over with your secret admirer,
你的真诚的微笑和真诚的微笑
letters and your kind smile and her genuine you are,
我认为你应该有一个自己的秘密仰慕者
and I think that you deserve a secret admirer of your own.
幸运的是
Luckily,
快走了
almost leaving.
找到狗狗
Locate dogmas.
啊
Ah.
所以工作时间和去米兰的行动开始表明我们进入了内部
So did the working hours and use the move to the rossoneri started showing that we get inside,
我可以这样做
so I can do that.
很多事情都是你自己做的
A lot of things have been working on yourself.
我想我会很努力的
I thought that I'd be hard.
70年翻译了大量的财富 有时与你捆绑在一起
Seventy translated a substantial wealth tied up at times with you.
或者你可以使用机械指定的会议你看起来绝对是令人震惊的 在过去的四天里他们一直很平静 当我看到他的时候
Or you can use mechanical designates the meeting you looked absolutely stunning and they've been so calm in the last four days and then right when I saw him.
这很紧张 因为你会很有趣
This is nervous as you are going to be fun,
我们将会是一次奇妙的旅程
we're going to have been an amazing journey.
嗯
Well,
我想我会看到你和你一起吃我的衣服
I guess I'll see you eating my outfit with you.
疯狂
Crazy.
或者你变高了
Or you got higher.
是的
Yeah,
这周我要给你一个马达 让你在地球上见到你 看看你的脸
I'll Ashley a motor through this week just to meet you on earth you to see your face.
我在这里找到了一个幸运的硬币
I found a lucky penny on my way here,
从我还是个小女孩的时候起
and ever since I was a little girl.
通常当我在我的道路上找到一个
Usually when I find one in my path,
我把它放在我的鞋里
I put it in my shoe,
所以我给你带来了你在机场找到的幸运的东西我把它放在你的牢房里你不需要去处理
so I brought you the lucky thing you found in the airport and I put this in your cell and you don't have to take issue.
嗯
Well,
现在 我们希望在你和我一起踏上这段旅程的路上 我能给你带来一些鼓励
now we hope that I'll bring you some encouragement on your way to here with me on this journey with me.
我看看我能不会做这个
I'll see if I do this.
你好
Hello,
我有一个孩子
I have a baby.
是吗
Are you?
如果你真的不能感谢你
If you really can't thank you.
你看起来不错 我想你知道你在这里
Have you looks good and I think you know you look right here.
多年来我在学校上课 我不知道
I class at school in years to I don't know,
让我们把它放在这里
let's put here,
我知道工会
I know unions,
克里斯
Chris,
我知道你是一个农民 可以从我的领域里跳出来
I know you are a farmer and can pop out of my field.
你不是疯了
You're not crazy,
你知道
you know,
农民们
farmers both,
我都是上面的人
I'm all the above,
你让我喘不过气来
you just took my breath away,
我知道你进去了 你要走了
and I know you get in there you are going to go,
你要让我喜欢辩论
you're going to make I like an argument.
他是谁
Who is he?
是的
Yeah,
yeah.
城镇
Town.
嗯
Well.
到目前为止
As goes so far,
哇
wow,
是的
yeah,
这是一米左右
this is a meter or so.
当你认为我是说这太神奇了
When you think I mean this is amazing.
美丽的女人 我觉得这是一个梦
Women beautiful and I feel like this is a dream,
梦想成真
a dream come true.
奥萨马需要打我
Osama needs to slap me.
我叫醒了我
I wake me up.
我说这是更好的
I said it's a better,
我醒着
I'm awake,
这将会发生
this is going to happen,
它将会发生zip
it's going to happen zip,
我想我把它拉到一起
and I guess I pull it together.
你想要在这些微小的事情上有多糟糕我指的是实际的水平
How bad do you want to get in the tiny things one I mean the levels can Actually.
我的意思是
I mean,
我知道
I know,
我不该这么说
I shouldn't say this,
但我的意思是
but I mean,
我不知道我是否准备好接受更多的层次
I don't know if I'm ready for more levels.
我准备好了现在就开始做节目
I'm ready to get started right now and just get the show on the road,
所以你在里面读
so you read ahead inside.
我准备好了
I am ready.
我们会做的
We'll do it go ahead.
所以除非你是独自一人
So unless you're on your own,
你会享受和度过一个美好的夜晚
you'll enjoy and have a good night.
我没有这个权利
I don't have the right.
会有更多的人看着我
there's going to be more looking at me like,
哦
Oh,
为什么不太可能重拾道德呢
why isn't much probably like to regain the moral?
我认为有很多
And I think there's a lot.
嗨
Hi.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy you versus here?
我不是真的
I'm not really,
哦
Oh,
我的上帝
my God,
我需要活着
I need to live,
留下来的人没有加入到你自己的队伍中 克里斯福克斯
stay didn't join yourselves overwhelmed grio Chris Fox sane,
并没有多少女孩感到困惑
and there's not that many girls are so confused.
这个休息
this break.
这是女士们的休息
This is a break of the ladies.
或者这是每个人
or is this everybody?
如果这是每个人都很了不起
If this is everybody that's amazing.
我想我一生中从未有过这种美丽的存在
I don't think I've ever been in the presence of this kind of beauty in my entire life.
我没想到克里斯哈里森会说
I didn't expect Chris Harrison to say,
去见见这些女人吧 考虑到这里只有15个女孩
Go meet these women considering the fact there's only fifteen girls here,
但是这个团队仍然比我通常的数据多出了14个
but this team is still a lot that is fourteen more than I usually data at one time.
你确定你不在这里吗
Are you guys sure you're not here?
隔壁有个聚会
There's a party next door.
司机的地址是错误的
The driver has the wrong address.
你想让我讲个笑话
You want me to tell a joke,
因为有时候如果我讲一个笑话
because sometimes if I tell a joke,
大家都笑了
everyone laughed.
也许我会先说 因为我很抱歉有充分的理由 你可以讲这个笑话
Maybe I'll talk first as you can tell the joke after I'm sorry for good reason.
在我那可怕的演讲之后 它可能会减轻人们的情绪
it might lighten the mood after my really horrible speech,
让我来屠杀它
let me massacre this,
然后我可以让每个人都开心
and then I could make everybody happy.
在所有的现实中
In all reality.
我一直在你们的问题上 我知道你们的工作有多重要 离开你们的家庭 让你们的工作留在这里
I've been in your guys issues and know how big a deal is to leave your families and leave your work to be here,
所以这意味着很多
so it means a lot.
这对我来说很重要
This is a big deal to me.
我知道爱可以在这里面发生
I know that love can happen in this.
让我们做自己
Let's just be ourselves,
这就是我所做的
and that's all I did.
如果你想让我成为世界上最幸运的人
And you know if you want me to be the luckiest man in the world.
让我们一起享受这段旅程吧
So let's enjoy this journey together.
这对我来说是非常重要的
This is so important to me to make this work.
我不在乎这批货
I don't care than the batch.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我在看电视节目
I'm on a TV show.
我要去见我的妻子
I'm meeting my wife.
这才是最重要的
That's what matters,
这是真实的 这是真实的
that's what's real and that's become real.
不
No,
好的
OK.
那么为什么海象要去特百惠派对呢
So why did the walrus go to the Tupperware party?
因为他想找到一个紧密的封印
Because he wanted to find a tight seal.
哦
Oh,
我的上帝
my God,
哦
oh,
我的上帝
my God,
我怎么能感觉到我可以用另一个词来形容尴尬 因为我和那些人一起笑 因为我不知道现在还能做什么
How can I feel that I can use another word of an awkward because I'll laugh along with those because I don't know what else to do right now.
我甚至都不明白
I don't even get it,
但那只是我 因为我是
but that's just me because I am.
有些东西没有点击
Some things not clicking up there,
所以你得到了荣誉
so you get the honor,
所有的人都在向其他人抱怨
all those who lies whimpering on the rest of the people.
我不知道
I don't know,
我想说 我们有15个 一般认为有25个
and I will say we have fifteen and think there's generally twenty five,
所以我不知道发生了什么
so I've no idea what's going on.
你知道他们将会是什么样子
You know what they're going to be.
我不知道
I don't know.
你不想说
Do you don't want to say,
是的
yeah,
我还想再买10个
I want ten more.
这是一个很有问题的问题
That's a loaded question.
它是
it is,
我很好
I'm okay,
我们诚实地说
we were honestly,
我将接受我的猜测
I'll take what I guess.
我们都希望能有更多的豪华轿车 还有5个女孩
We were all expecting to more limos full of five more girls.
我想今晚会有更多的人来这里
I think there's more people come more can't come tonight.
他已经做了一个我们不是格里格斯的演讲
He already made a speech which which we weren't griggs.
好的
OK,
我看过这个节目
I've watched the show,
我们如何生活
How can we life?
至少有二十五个女孩
There's always been at least twenty five girls,
所以
so.
昨晚你变得更紧张了吗
Are you getting more nervous and last night?
我不紧张
I'm not nervous.
就像神圣一样
It's like holy.
这些是怎么回事
how all these?
也许所有这些女人
Maybe all these women,
每个人都记得很多年的名字
and everybody do you remember any names for years,
我变得如此孤独
and I got so lonely.